TEJASWINI MORE

Software Developer

E: tejaswini9605@gmail.com

P: 7768056490

L: www.linkedin.com/in/ tejaswini-more

A: Pune, 411028, India

Nationality:

Indian

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Bulma, Buefy

Javascript

Node.js

Expressjs

fastify

Vuejs

Angular

PHP, Laravel 8

MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL

GitLab

WordPress

LANGUAGES

English

Marathi

Hindi

PROFILE

Over 4+ years of IT and hands-on experience in application development. I am full stack developer with knowledge in many different front end and backend languages, responsive frameworks and databases. My objective is simply to be the best developer that I can be and contribute to the technology industry.

EDUCATION

BE(E&TC) | Sinhgad Academy of Engineering, Pune, Pune

Jul 2013 - Jul 2017

64%

HSC | R.R.Shinde College, Pune, Pune

Jul 2011 - Jun 2013

56%

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer | Firstcry.com, Pune

May 2021

- Created a new e-commerce websitefrom the ground up. Experience with configuration, and development of e-commerceplatform.
- Participated in the entire phase of development cycle from design, testing, and implementation.
- Worked with e-commerce databases to develop inventory management, cart management, ordering and billing management.
- Implemented UI design using VueJs, Bulma and Buefy. Built RESTful API using Nodejs fastify and sequelize ORM.

Web Developer | Angelsoft Technology Pvt. Ltd., Pune

Mar 2020 - May 2021

- Working as a senior web developer for developing the components which are used by several teams.
- Used Bootstrap and Angular UI to make the application user-friendly in the development of the Navigation Bar, Tables, Sliders, Calendars etc. Building PHP websites using PHP based frameworks like Laravel 8.
- Experienced indevelopingweb pages usingHTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3,
 JavaScript,Angular,jQuery, Bootstrap, NodeJS, Ajax. Have experience with
 using Node.js to interact with MongoDB.
- MEAN Stack development experience (Mongo dB, Express, NodeJS, Angular)

Software Engineer | ASP OL Media Pvt. Ltd.

Oct 2017 - Oct 2018

- CMS development experience with WordPress. Customize themes to meet client's requirements.
- Worked on Namecheap, Hostinger, Sentora, Bigrock, and WHM for hosting Domains. Expertise in hand-coding cross-browser and cross-platform HTML5 and CSS3.
- Experience in working with RESTful API's using Node.js.